Guide to the John Ewart Wallace Sterling, Chancellor of Stanford University, Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Series 1
  - Alphabetical files
    - University of Toronto - Class of '27 (Victoria College), Pre-1950s (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - University of Tulsa (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Victoria College - Victoria, B.C. (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - University of Western Ontario (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - York University - Toronto, Canada (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - J.E. Wallace Sterling, 1973 (Box 11A, Folder 1)
    - Kenworthy Letter to Sterling, 1973 July (Box 11A, Folder 2)
    - Pearson Letter: $11,000,000 Anonymous Matching Fund, 1973 Aug. (Box 11A, Folder 3)
    - Stanford University's Life Income Plans, 1973 June (Box 11A, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Trustee - Associate Development Board, undated (Box 11A, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Activities and Donations by Faculty, 1973 Nov. 6 (Box 11A, Folder 6)
    - Gifts of Restricted Stock, 1973 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 7)
    - Excerpts from Robert Conway Memo, 1973 Dec. 18 (Box 11A, Folder 8)
    - James G. Boswell, II, AB '47, 1973 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 9)
    - Theodore Achilles, AB'26, 1973 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 10)
    - Ambassador and Mrs. Walter Annenberg, 1973 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 11)
    - Campaign Leadership Prospect Review, 1973 Dec. 7 (Box 11A, Folder 12)
    - Mrs. Gates Baldwin (Florence), 1973 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 13)
    - Handwritten notes, undated (Box 11A, Folder 14)
    - Letters to Sterling, 1973 (Box 11A, Folder 15)
    - Cuthbertson letter to Joseph M. Thomas, 1973 Nov. 2 (Box 11A, Folder 16)
    - Dick McCurdy; Dailey letter to Sterling, 1973 Oct. (Box 11A, Folder 17)
    - Handwritten Notes, undated (Box 11A, Folder 18)
    - Ressel V. Lee, 1973 Feb. (Box 11A, Folder 19)
    - Virgil Kauffman, 1973 Nov. (Box 11A, Folder 20)
    - Jon Cosovich, Kenneth Cuthbertson, Daniel K. Ludwig, 1973 Oct. (Box 11A, Folder 21)
    - Letter from Hays to Rodriguez, 1974 April (Box 11A, Folder 22)
    - W. Clement Stone Foundation, 1974 June (Box 11A, Folder 23)
    - Ted Swigart, 1974 June (Box 11A, Folder 24)
    - "Best" Prospects: $250,000+, 1974 Feb. 22 (Box 11A, Folder 25)
    - William M. Roth and Mrs. William P. Roth, 1973 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 26)
    - $50,000 Pledge from Katherine Graham, 1974 Jan. (Box 11A, Folder 27)
    - Mrs/. Launcelot Gamble, 1973 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 28)
    - Committee on Finance and Development, 1973-1974 (Box 11A, Folder 29)
    - Letter from Cuthbertson to Korton, 1974 April 5 (Box 11A, Folder 30)
    - Moody Foundation, Galveston, Texas, 1974 April (Box 11A, Folder 31)
    - Single Men in Bay Area, undated (Box 11A, Folder 32)
    - John Stauffer Charitable Trust, 1976 Feb. (Box 11A, Folder 33)
    - John E. and John F. Elliott Fund, undated (Box 11A, Folder 34)
    - Kresge Foundation, 1974 June (Box 11A, Folder 35)
    - New Main Library Building General Planning Protocol, 1975 March 31 (Box 11A, Folder 36)
    - Mrs. Thomas Peterson, Cleveland, Ohio, 1975 March (Box 11A, Folder 37)
    - Mrs. Alan J. Rosenberg, 1975 Jan. (Box 11A, Folder 38)
    - Hugh Metzgar - Irvine Foundation, 1975 March (Box 11A, Folder 39)
    - Carl F. Braun Trust/John Braun, 1974 Dec.-1975 Jan. (Box 11A, Folder 40)
    - Letter from Thomas A. Stamey, 1975 March (Box 11A, Folder 41)
    - Charitable Gifts of Closely Held Stock, 1974 Oct. 14 (Box 11A, Folder 42)
    - Mrs. Edward H. Heller, Atherton, 1974 Jan. (Box 11A, Folder 43)
    - John Braun and C.F. Braun Trust, 1972 March (Box 11A, Folder 44)
    - Donn B. Tatum, 1971 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 45)
    - Possible Gift Opportunities for S.D. Bechtel, Sr., 1975 Jan. 15 (Box 11A, Folder 46)
    - Letter from Taylor to Sterling, 1971 Feb. 18 (Box 11A, Folder 47)
    - Robert S. falkenhagen '40, Portland, Oregon, 1972 May (Box 11A, Folder 48)
    - Luce Foundation, 1972 May (Box 11A, Folder 49)
    - New York Major Gifts Committee, 1972 May (Box 11A, Folder 50)
    - Letter from Eberle to Jon Cosovich, 1975 June-July (Box 11A, Folder 51)
    - L.W. Lane, Jr., 1975 April (Box 11A, Folder 52)
    - Theodore E. sigart, Houston, Texas, 1974 Nov. (Box 11A, Folder 53)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Arnold Beckman, 1973 Aug. (Box 11A, Folder 54)
    - Michale Oman, 1974 July 26 (Box 11A, Folder 55)
    - Edward Willingham Arnold, 1974 July 15 (Box 11A, Folder 56)
    - Robert C. Swain, Ab'28, Riverside, Connecticut, 1974 Oct. 25 (Box 11A, Folder 57)
    - Joseph McMicking, 1974 Aug. (Box 11A, Folder 58)
    - Mrs. Dudley Swim, 1974 Oct. (Box 11A, Folder 59)
    - William Mansur Hume, 1974 Oct. (Box 11A, Folder 60)
    - Steve Bechtel Family, 1974 Sept. (Box 11A, Folder 61)
    - J. Erik Jonsson, Dallas, 1974 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 62)
    - Letter to Leonard K. Firestone, 1974 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 63)
    - Max C. Fleishmann Foundation, 1974 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 64)
    - Henry Hoagland - Boston, 1973 April (Box 11A, Folder 65)
    - Katherine Graham, Washington D.C., 1974 Oct. (Box 11A, Folder 66)
    - Standard Research Worksheet, 1974 Sept. 18-19 (Box 11A, Folder 67)
    - Lewis W. Spitz, 1974 Sept. (Box 11A, Folder 68)
    - William mansur Hume, 1974 Sept. (Box 11A, Folder 69)
    - Kim Firestone and the Firestone Foundation, 1974 Dec. 3 (Box 11A, Folder 70)
    - Shell Companies Foundation, 1974 Aug. (Box 11A, Folder 71)
    - Walter A. Haas and Lucie Stern Estate Trust, 1974 May (Box 11A, Folder 72)
    - Kimball C. Firestone and the Firestone Foundation, 1974 May (Box 11A, Folder 73)
    - The Pew Charitable Trusts, 1974 May (Box 11A, Folder 71)
    - Meeting with Mr. William R. Pagen, 1973 Sept. 13 (Box 11A, Folder 72)
    - Daniel K. Ludwig, 1975 March (Box 11A, Folder 73)
    - Charles Leigh Wheeler, Sr. - Pope & Talbot, Inc., 1975 Jan. (Box 11A, Folder 74)
    - H.L. Hunt Estate, 1975 Jan. (Box 11A, Folder 75)
    - Paul hertelendy, 1972 Nov. 17 (Box 11A, Folder 76)
    - Major Gift Proposal, 1971 Dec. 2 (Box 11A, Folder 77)
    - Stephen D. Bechtel, Jr., 1972 Nov. (Box 11A, Folder 78)
    - Paul Hertelendy, 1972 Nov. (Box 11A, Folder 79)
    - Thomas G. McGuire, 1972 Dec.1 (Box 11A, Folder 80)
    - Family of George Ditz, Sr., 1973 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 81)
    - Letter to Pike, 1972 Jan. (Box 11A, Folder 82)
    - Ben Swig, 1972 Oct. (Box 11A, Folder 83)
    - Likelihood of Attendance Cabinet Meeting, 1972 Nov. 13 (Box 11A, Folder 84)
    - A New Building for the Stanford Law School, 1972 March (Box 11A, Folder 85)
    - Christian de Guigne, 1974 Jan. (Box 11A, Folder 86)
    - Chandler Institute of Communication Proposal, 1973 March 22 (Box 11A, Folder 87)
    - The Chandler Proposal, 1973 March 12 (Box 11A, Folder 88)
    - Mrs. Dudley Swim, 1974 April (Box 11A, Folder 89)
    - Norman Brant Chandler, oldest son of Otis Chandler, 1973 March 16 (Box 11A, Folder 90)
    - letter from Spangler to Jordan, 1974 Aug. (Box 11A, Folder 91)
    - James Irvine Foundation, 1974 July (Box 11A, Folder 92)
    - Letter from Cosovich to Eberle, 1975 July (Box 11A, Folder 93)
    - Dr. Robert C. Swain, 1973 March (Box 11A, Folder 94)
    - Henry W. Hoagland, Jr. (Harry), 1973 March 19 (Box 11A, Folder 95)
    - Letter from Bechtel to Ehrlich, 1974 May (Box 11A, Folder 96)
    - James Irvine Foundation, 1975 Aug. 8 (Box 11A, Folder 97)
    - Geographical Listing of Major Gift Volunteers, 1975 Aug. (Box 11A, Folder 98)
    - Letter from Cuthbertson to Burris, 1975 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 99)
    - John E. and John F. Elliott Fund, undated (Box 11A, Folder 100)
    - Volunteer Assignments, 1974 Feb. 7 (Box 11A, Folder 101)
    - Selected Unassigned Prospects, 1974 Feb. 8 (Box 11A, Folder 102)
    - Sid W. Richardson Foundation, 1975 Feb. 28 (Box 11A, Folder 103)
    - Christian de Guigne III, 1975 April (Box 11A, Folder 104)
    - David Mitchell and Anonymous Client, 1972 Dec. (Box 11A, Folder 105)
    - New Orleans Visit, 1973 Feb. (Box 11A, Folder 106)
    - Various letters, 1972-1973 (Box 11A, Folder 107)
    - Assigned Major Gift List, 1975 Oct. (Box 11A, Folder 108)
    - Christian de Guigne III, 1975 April 21 (Box 11A, Folder 109)
    - Report of Gifts Received, 1977 (Box 11A, Folder 110)
    - Major Gift Committee Members, 1977 March 8 (Box 11A, Folder 111)
    - Samples of 1976-1977 Fourth Mail Appeal, 1977 March 16 (Box 11A, Folder 112)
    - Major Gift Volunteers, 1977 April 8 (Box 11A, Folder 113)
    - Memorandum for the Campaign for Stanford, 1977 (Box 11B, Folder 2)
    - Various Letters and Memorandums re the Stanford Gift Program, 1976-1977 (Box 11B, Folder 3)
    - Journalism, 1971 (Box 11B, Folder 4)
    - The Campaign for Stanford, 1972-1977 (Box 11B, Folder 5)
    - The Campaign for Stanford - Gift Opportunities, 1972-1977 (Box 11B, Folder 6)
    - Stanford R-Plan Manual, 1971 (Box 11B, Folder 7)
    - The Campaign for Stanford - Campaign Plans, 1972 (Box 11B, Folder 8)
    - Program Statements Super-Priority Projects, 1970 (Box 11B, Folder 9)
    - The Campaign for Stanford - updates, 1972 (Box 11B, Folder 10)
    - Major Gift Chairman Meeting, 1973 (Box 11B, Folder 11)
    - Northern California / Hawaii Major Gifts Committee Meeting, 1976 Feb 24 (Box 11B, Folder 12)
    - The Campaign for Stanford folders and Financial Reviews, 1971-1972 (Box 11B, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (1/9), 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (2/9), 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence (3/9), 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (4/9), 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (5/9), 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (6/9), 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence 7/9), 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (8/9), 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (9/9), 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - National War College Correspondence, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Huntington Library - Reports, Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Personal Materials, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Roll Books, 1945-1947 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Various Books and Pamphlets, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Lectures/ Academia
      - Various New York Times Newspapers, 1955-1956 (Box 13A, Folder 1)
      - Ancient History - Greece and Rome, undated (Box 13A, Folder 2)
      - Modern Europe - 16th/17th century, undated (Box 13A, Folder 3)
      - Napolean Bonaparte, undated (Box 13A, Folder 4)
      - French Revolution, undated (Box 13A, Folder 5)
      - 19th Century Diplomacy, undated (Box 13A, Folder 6)
      - Capitalism, undated (Box 13A, Folder 7)
      - Nationalism, undated (Box 13A, Folder 8)
      - Religion, undated (Box 13A, Folder 9)
      - Russia, 1938 (Box 13A, Folder 10)
      - The War and Peace, 1933 (Box 13A, Folder 11)
      - European Imperialism, 1928-1929 (Box 13A, Folder 12)
      - Leads - Education Reading, 1949 (Box 13A, Folder 13)
      - Trends in Higher Education, 1947-1949 (Box 13A, Folder 14)
      - C.T. History 1C Notebooks, 1947 (Box 13A, Folder 15)
      - C.T. History Lectures, undated (Box 13A, Folder 16)
      - C.T. History 2V Notebook, 1945-1946 (Box 13A, Folder 17)
      - C.T. History of Russia, 1947 (Box 13A, Folder 18)
      - England, undated (Box 13A, Folder 19)
      - C.T. Current History H 5, 1946-1947 (Box 13A, Folder 20)
      - Germany 19th Century, undated (Box 13A, Folder 21)
      - Russian Revolution, undated (Box 13A, Folder 22)
      - N.W.C. Notes, 1947 (Box 13A, Folder 23)
      - Medieval Europe, 1926 (Box 13A, Folder 24)
      - Science, undated (Box 13A, Folder 25)
      - Biographical Bits, undated (Box 13A, Folder 26)
      - Churchill's Speeches, 1942-1947 (Box 13A, Folder 27)
      - Great Britain - Domestic Affairs, 1947 (Box 13A, Folder 28)
      - Dominions, 1947-1948 (Box 13A, Folder 29)
      - Pasadena Public Library Board, 1946 (Box 13A, Folder 30)
      - Lectures - The Russian Riddle, undated (Box 13A, Folder 31)
      - The Changing Pattern and the Abiding Purpose of Education, undated (Box 13A, Folder 32)
      - Lectures - Dumbarton Oaks, 1945 (Box 13A, Folder 33)
      - Lectures - The Professor and the Microphone, undated (Box 13A, Folder 34)
      - Lectures - Problems of Education in Peace Making, 1945 (Box 13A, Folder 35)
      - Lectures - Problems of Peacemaking, 1943 (Box 13A, Folder 36)
      - Lectures - Russia and Crisis, 1947 (Box 13A, Folder 37)
      - Lectures - Side Lights on the San Francisco Conference, undated (Box 13A, Folder 38)
      - The Struggle in Europe, undated (Box 13A, Folder 39)
      - Lectures - Technology - A Frankenstein?, undated (Box 13A, Folder 40)
      - Lecture - United Nations in Review and in Prospect, 1946-1947 (Box 13A, Folder 41)
      - Lectures - USA and the Search for Peace, 1947 April 7 (Box 13A, Folder 42)
      - Lectures - US Post-War World, 1943 December 7 (Box 13A, Folder 43)
      - Lectures - The United States and the Refugee Problem, undated (Box 13A, Folder 44)
      - Lectures - The United Nations in Review & Prospects, undated (Box 13A, Folder 45)
      - War and Peace: Thirty Year Perspective, 1948 Nov 11 (Box 13A, Folder 46)
      - Lectures - What About Russia?, 1943 August (Box 13A, Folder 47)
      - Lectures - What Price Peace?, undated (Box 13A, Folder 48)
      - Lectures - Will Russia Cooperate?, 1943 Nov 1 (Box 13A, Folder 49)
      - Public Lectures - What is a Constitutional Convention?, undated (Box 13A, Folder 50)
      - Lectures - What was wrong with Versailles?, undated (Box 13A, Folder 51)
      - Lectures - H2, 1939 (Box 13A, Folder 53)
      - Lectures - The Age of Reason, 1942 May 26 (Box 13A, Folder 54)
      - World Trade, 1947 May 19 (Box 13A, Folder 52)
      - Lectures - European History, 1937 July 15 (Box 13A, Folder 55)
      - Lectures - The Beginnings of Economic Imperialism, undated (Box 13A, Folder 56)
      - Capitalism and its Critics, undated (Box 13A, Folder 57)
      - Lectures - Central and Southeastern Europe, undated (Box 13A, Folder 58)
      - Lectures - The Commercial Revolution, undated (Box 13A, Folder 59)
      - Lectures - The End of an Era, undated (Box 13A, Folder 60)
      - England in the 17th Century, undated (Box 13A, Folder 61)
      - Lectures - England 1689-1763, undated (Box 13A, Folder 62)
      - Lectures - Great Britain, undated (Box 13A, Folder 63)
      - Lectures - Napoleon and the Great Man Theory, undated (Box 13A, Folder 64)
      - Lectures - Notes on Magna Carta, undated (Box 13A, Folder 65)
      - Lectures - Occupied Europe Looks at the Future, undated (Box 13A, Folder 66)
      - Lectures - Responsible Government in British Empire, undated (Box 13A, Folder 67)
      - Lectures - Rise of Japan, undated (Box 13A, Folder 68)
      - Lectures - The Rise of Russia, undated (Box 13A, Folder 69)
      - Lectures - Russia and the War, undated (Box 13A, Folder 70)
      - Lectures - Sea Power in Days of Nelson, undated (Box 13A, Folder 71)
      - Lectures - Socialism and Mid-Century Revolutions, undated (Box 13A, Folder 72)
      - Lectures - The 3rd French Republic, undated (Box 13A, Folder 73)
      - Lectures - The Search for Security, undated (Box 13A, Folder 74)
      - Lectures - Spanish Revolt, undated (Box 13A, Folder 75)
      - Lectures - Terror as an Instrument of Policy, undated (Box 13A, Folder 76)
      - Lectures - The War at Sea, undated (Box 13A, Folder 77)
      - Lectures - War Economics and Neutrality, undated (Box 13A, Folder 78)
      - Lectures - The War of 1812, undated (Box 13A, Folder 79)
      - Lectures - Personal, 1947 (Box 13A, Folder 80)
      - America: Between War and Peace, 1948 (Box 13A, Folder 81)
      - A Tide in the Affairs of Men, undated (Box 13A, Folder 82)
      - Lectures - American History, undated (Box 13A, Folder 83)
      - Lectures - Armistice Day -- 25 Years After, 1943 Nov 11 (Box 13A, Folder 84)
      - Lectures - British-American Relations, undated (Box 13A, Folder 85)
      - Lectures - Choice Before Us, 1943 Oct 22 (Box 13A, Folder 86)
      - Lectures - The Foreign Policy of the United States, undated (Box 13A, Folder 87)
      - Lectures - The House of Morgan, undated (Box 13A, Folder 88)
      - Lectures - Imperialism and Trusteeship, 1948 Apr 12 (Box 13A, Folder 89)
      - Lectures - Whither France, undated (Box 13A, Folder 90)
      - Lectures - Conflict and Crisis in Europe, 1948 Jan 8 (Box 13A, Folder 91)
      - Lectures: Conflicting Ideologies in Europe, undated (Box 13b, Folder 1)
      - Lectures: "Imperialism and Trusteeship", 1946 June 19 (Box 13b, Folder 2)
      - "Let Freedom Ring", undated (Box 13b, Folder 3)
      - Lectures: "Lincoln: His Credo and His Country", 1946 Dec. 12 (Box 13b, Folder 4)
      - Lectures: "Patterns in Peace Making", undated (Box 13b, Folder 5)
      - Lectures: "Peace Objectives of the British", 1941 Feb. 2 (Box 13b, Folder 6)
    - Great Britain (General), 1945-1948 (Box 13b, Folder 7)
    - Great Britain Anglos-Soviet Alliance, 1947 (Box 13b, Folder 8)
    - Election, July 1945, 1945 July-Aug. (Box 13b, Folder 9)
    - Army and Navy, 1944-1946 (Box 13b, Folder 10)
    - Attlee's Speeches, 1945-1946 (Box 13b, Folder 11)
    - Great Britain (Divider, No Contents), undated (Box 13b, Folder 12)
    - C.B.S. Citizen's Forum, 1945-1946 (Box 13b, Folder 13)
    - Personal - Public Lectures, 1942-1945 (Box 13b, Folder 14)
    - Britain Clippings, 1956 (Box 13b, Folder 15)
    - Canada-Clippings, 1955-1956 (Box 13b, Folder 16)
    - Foundation, 1955-1956 (Box 13b, Folder 17)
    - France (Empty Folder), undated (Box 13b, Folder 18)
    - United Nations, 1955 (Box 13b, Folder 19)
    - Foundations, 1954-1955 (Box 13b, Folder 20)
    - Canada & Britain (Miscellaneous), 1954-1955 (Box 13b, Folder 21)
    - Canada & Britain (Trade, Business, & Finance), 1955 (Box 13b, Folder 22)
    - Academic Freedom, 1954-1955 (Box 13b, Folder 23)
    - Canada & Britain World Affairs, 1955 (Box 13b, Folder 24)
    - Refugees, 1952-1954 (Box 13b, Folder 25)
    - American Bible Society 150th Anniversary Celebration, 1965-1967 (Box 14a, Folder 1)
    - American Institute for Forign Trade, 1965 June-July (Box 14a, Folder 2)
    - Bayne, The Rt. Rev. Stephen F., Jr., 1959-1974 (Box 14a, Folder 3)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 14a, Folder 4)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 14a, Folder 5)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation, 1960-1968 (Box 14a, Folder 6)
    - California Traffic Safety Foundation, 1958-1969 (Box 14a, Folder 7)
    - The Century Association, 1954-1970 (Box 14a, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Economic Development Correspondence, 1963-1973 (Box 14a, Folder 9)
    - Commitee on Economic Devlopment Minutes of Meetings, 1958-1966 (Box 14a, Folder 10)
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education, 1967-1972 (Box 14a, Folder 11)
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education Trustee Meeting Minutes, 1967-1969 (Box 14a, Folder 12)
    - Leon W. Delbridge, 1952-1972 (Box 14a, Folder 13)
    - George A. Ditz, 1970-1971 (Box 14a, Folder 14)
    - "Foreign Relations of the United States" Advisory Committee, 1964-1969 (Box 14a, Folder 15)
    - Funk & Wagnallis (Consulting and Advisory), 1956-1970 (Box 14a, Folder 16)
    - Carl Hayden, 1971-1972 (Box 14a, Folder 17)
    - Health Science Facilities Bond Issue Committee, 1972 (Box 14a, Folder 18)
    - Hoover Commission and Hoover Report, Citizens Committee for, 1955-1958 (Box 14a, Folder 19)
    - Independence Life Insurance Company of America, 1957-1967 (Box 14a, Folder 20)
    - Bud Linn, 1953-1966 (Box 14a, Folder 21)
    - Sir Douglas Logan, 1953-1957 (Box 14a, Folder 22)
  - Bicentennial
    - United States Bicentennial World Exposition Technical Report, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Letters from Sales Ammunition Inc., Puerto Rincan Historical Calendar and Negro Historical Calendar, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Time News magazine Article: Environment, 1969 Sept. 12 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Parade: A Call to Action, 1969 Sept. 21 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - The Bostonian Newspaper Volume 1, Number 1, 1969 Sept. 20 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - A Monument to Democracy, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission: A New Spirit for '76, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Letter from Charles Wilkinson (White House) about Bicentennial, 1969 May 8 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - The United States Bicentennial Celebration: A Framework for Nationwide Participation, 1970 May 7 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco Examiner: History of War in Newspaper Front Pages, 1941-1945 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Letter from U.S. Senator Charles Mathias, 1971 Dec. 20 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Letter from U.S. Secretary of Commerce, 1970 April 6 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Letter from U.S. Department of Labor, 1970 April 16 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Letter from Federal Comminications Commisson, 1970 April 15 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Toward a Meanigful Bicentennial, 1969 Sept. 24 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - "Men At Their Best" Captain Leo Stanley Sec. I-II, 1969 Nov. 12 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - "Men At Their Best" Section III-IV, circa 1969 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Black and White Photos: University of York, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - "Men At Their Best" Section V-VI, circa 1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Letter from Skidmor, Owings & Merrill, 1970 March (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Department of Interior: American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1969 July 28 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Preliminary Report of the Secretary of the Interior to the American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1969 Dec. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - When There is Vision: A Portfolio of Suggestions for Dar celebration of the 200th Anniversary of the United States of America (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Back to the People: A report to the American Revolution Bicentennial Commission by Mike McManus, undated (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Draft Legislation to Accompany a Proposal for the Redevelopment of Pennsylvania Avenue, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Letters from Urban Design and Development Corporation Established by the American Institute of Architects and Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars, 1969 April 30, July 14 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Corporation for Public Broadcasting, 1970 April (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Taking the Bicentennial Seriously, 1974 April 1 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Tube: Trans Urban Bicentennial Exposition, 1969 Sept. 14 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - The Spirit of '76: Program Considerations and Objectives, 1970 June (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - The Commision and Goals for '76, 1970 May 4 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Letter from American Revolution Bicentennial Commission: Henderson Supplee, Jr., 1970 June 29 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Letter from Federal Trade Commission, 1970 Feb. 5 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Letter from the Secretary of Transportation, 1970 Jan. 27 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Letter from Export-Import bank of the United States, 1970 Jan. 26 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Letter from Director of Naval history, 1970 Feb. 19 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Suggestions & Comments for Rewrite of ARBC Report, 1970 May 26 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Letter from Secretary of Commerce: Philadelphia Bicentennial Proposal Revision, 1970 May (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Letter frin American Revolution Bicentennial Comission, 1970 June 17 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - A Proposal for the Redevelopment of Pennsylvania Avenue, undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Letter from Showalter to Stans, Secretary of Commerce, 1970 July (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Fort Louderdale News: Mike Morgan, 1969 June 18 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - The Franklin Mint, 1971 Oct. 20 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Highlights of Progress to Date, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Pre-Federal Maps in the National Archives: an Annotated List, 1971 Nov. 15 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission of Texas, 1971 June 7 (Box 18, Folder 6)